This is another type of Udacity workspace.
这是另一种类型的优达学城 workspace
It's an IDE or integrated development environment,
这是一个 IDE 或集成开发环境
which provides tools for writing software.
提供了编写软件的工具
It's got a file browser,
有文件浏览器
a terminal, and a code editor.
终端和代码编辑器
Here, I've set up a Flask app for you,
我在这里为你设置了一个 Flask 应用
and I'm going to give a tour of the different files.
先来介绍一下这些不同文件
First, there's the worldbank.py file.
首先 worldbank.py 文件
This is the file you'll run in the terminal to start the Web app.
这是你将在终端中运行以启动 Web 应用的文件
This file is importing something called App from the worldbankapp folder.
此文件从 worldbankapp 文件夹导入 app
You'll see what this app is in a minute.
你马上就能看到这个 app 是什么
When the application runs,
应用程序运行时
it'll be on port 3,001 as you can see here in the port attribute.
在端口 3001 上 你可以在 port 属性中看到
What's inside this worldbankapp folder?
worldbankapp 文件夹里面有什么?
There's an init file which means I've set this up like a Python package.
有一个 init 文件 这意味着我将其设置为了 Python 软件包
When the package is run,
当软件包运行时
the init file gets run first.
首先运行 init 文件
Here's the init file.
这就是 init 文件
First, I'm importing the Flask library and then I create a variable called app,
首先 导入 flask 库 然后创建一个名为 app 的变量
and finally import the routes file.
最后导入 routes 文件
It's a bit tricky to see how all of these lines of
理解这些相关文件中的代码如何协同工作 会有些棘手
If I'm in the workspace directory in the terminal,
如果我在终端的 workspace 目录中
I start the app by running 'python worldbank.py'.
可以运行 'python worldbank.py' 来启动应用
I'm going to open a terminal and run 'python worldbank.py'.
我要打开一个终端并运行 'python worldbank.py'
This init file is run and imports the app variable as well as the routes file.
init 文件运行 导入了 app 变量以及 routes 文件
If you're not following the logic of all this,
如果你没有完全理解这些代码的逻辑
don't worry about it too much.
不用太担心
You don't need to understand all of this to build the app itself.
构建应用并不需要完全理解这些内容
The actual code you'll need to change is in
你需要修改的实际代码是
routes.py and the files in the template folder.
routes.py 和 template 文件夹中的文件
The routes.py and template folders are where the magic happens.
routes.py 和 template 文件夹是 "奇迹" 所在
These are the files and folders you'll actually be working with.
这些是你实际上需要完成的工作
In routes.py, I'm importing this app variable at the top.
在 routes.py 中 我在顶部导入这个 app 变量
Then, I'm importing the render template method from the Flask library.
然后从 flask 库导入 render_template 方法
Render template, as you'll see,
稍后你将看到 render_template 就是
is going to specify what HTML file should show up based on a Web address.
根据 Web 地址指定应显示内容 HTML 文件
This first chunk of code says,
第一块代码的意思是
that if the user goes to the homepage like www.udacity.com
如果用户访问网站主页 比如 www.udacity.com
or www.udacity.com/index or whatever your Webpage is called,
或 www.udacity.com/index 或你的其他网站名称
then the index.html should render.
那么应该渲染 index.html
The second example says,
第二个例子是说
if I go to the Webpage name,
如果转到网页名称
and then type /project-one,
然后输入 /project-one
then the project_one.html file should render.
应该渲染 project_one.html 文件
These HTML files are in the templates folder.
这些 HTML 文件位于 templates 文件夹中
So, again you specify the Web address in @app.route,
再次说明 在 @app.route 中指定 Web 地址
then you specify the html file to serve in the render template method.
然后指定传入到 render_template 方法的 HTML 文件
The functions like index and
index 和 project_one 这样的函数可以任意命名
Your own computer can create a local backend server while you develop an app.
你自己的计算机可以在开发应用时 创建一个本地的后端服务器
So, likewise, in the classroom you can spin
所以 同样地 在教室里你也可以启动
up a backend server to see how your Web app renders.
一个后端服务器来查看 Web 应用的渲染效果
You just need to know what website to put into your browser.
你只需要知道在浏览器输入什么地址即可
Actually, I already started the Web app when I typed 'python worldbank.py'.
实际上 当我输入 'python worldbank.py' 时 就已经启动了 Web 应用
So, I'm going to shut down the Web app first by hitting Control-C.
所以 我先点击 Control-C 来关闭应用
Okay. So, first you need to know
好的 首先你需要知道
what website to put into your browser in order to see your website.
在浏览器中放入什么网址可以来查看你的网站
For the classroom, what you'll have to do is type env,
在教室中 你要做的就是输入 env
then the pipe, grep WORK.
然后管道 | grep WORK
The env command shows all the environmental variables of the workspace.
env 命令显示 workspace 的所有环境变量
What the env pipeline grep WORK command does,
env | grep WORK 命令的作用
is filter out the environmental variables for
就是筛选出变量名包含 WORK 的环境变量
The Web address is going to be this workspace ID followed
Web 地址就是这个 WORKSPACEID 后面接
by dash 3001 a dot and then the workspace domain.
-3001. 然后是这个 WORKSPACEDOMAIN
I'll put instructions below the video as well.
我也会在视频下方附加说明
Now, when you execute the worldbank.py file, you'll start the server.
现在 执行 worldbank.py 文件时 服务器就会启动
Then, type 'python worldbank.py'.
输入 'python worldbank.py'
Now, it says the server is running on port 3,001.
现在 它说服务器正在端口 3001 上运行
Now, putting the correct Web address in a browser, you can see the app.
现在 在浏览器中放入正确的 Web 地址 就可以看到该应用
Here's the app. This is the index.html page.
应用显示出来了 这是 index.html 页面
Now, if I put in project-one,
现在 如何在链接中放入 project-one
I can see the project_one.html page.
可以看到 project_one.html 页面
Going back to the workspace,
回到 workspace
I'm going to open these templates and you can see that
打开这些模板 你可以看到
they're just HTML and this was the HTML being rendered.
它们只是 HTML 这就是刚才渲染的那些 HTML
In fact, you can change the HTML.
实际上你可以修改这些 HTML
Everything will automatically be saved in the workspace.
workspace 中一切都会自动保存
Now, you can see if you refresh the Web page with your Web app,
现在 如果刷新页面的话 你可以看到
than the HTML automatically updated.
HTML 会自动更新
Next, you'll do an exercise to expand
接下来 你将进行练习
this Web app and get used to all of the routes and templates.
扩展这个 Web 应用 习惯这些路由和模板